# **Jonathan Connors**

Application Administration: Successfully implemented ITSM software for DLR group, Managed project from beginning to end, continued to configure software as needed, loading data, licensing, maintenance, changes required by clients, and minimizing downtime.

Vendor management: Negotiated licensing contract, reconfigured and introduced new licensing model saving the company 90k annually.

Automation: Created automation process to automate software installations using SCCM, InTune and Fresh service.

Process Creation: Implemented and designed workstation build process, taking the build time from 30 days to next day service.

Technical training: Creation and execution of multi-day training sessions and single session webinars. Directed toward both technicians and end users at both customer sites and in a training center environment.

Technical communication: Able to convey highly technical information to people with varying levels of technical expertise in a way that is usable by them. Communicates well with everyone from developers to end users.

Experienced IT Professional with over 20 years of experience in system and site administration. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.





2019-08 -2021-02

# **Work History**

### **Address**

Lynnwood, WA, 98036

### **Phone**

425.443.7121

#### E-mail

JonathanLConnors@gmail.c om



**Active Directory** 

Vendor Management

Change management

Contract negotiations

## **Application Manager**

DLRGroup, Seattle, WA

- Primary owner of IT ticket system application (Fresh Service) owned application form inquiry to successful implementation.
- Automation of software installation from ticket system storefront with intune and sccm.
- Automated small item purchasing integrating ticketing system with outside vendor.
- Created change management process in ticketing system.
- Vendor management.
- Configured, installed, and supported Architectural software including AutoCAD, Revit Navisworks, ARCgis.
- Configured, installed, and supported Electrical engineering software including AGI32 ELUM tools.

Customer relations
Disaster recovery planning
Negotiations
Purchasing
Mentoring
Needs analysis
Phone system (VOIP)
Notebook Computers
Server configuration
Desktop support
HP Servers
AutoCAD
Relationship-Building

## 2011-06 - DLRGroup, Northwest IT Manager

Seattle, Washington

2019-08

- IT generalist responsible for the daily operation of the northwest region for DLRGroup.
- Onsite support for 100 users.
- Responsible for all server configuration.
- Desktop support for entire region (Windows 7 and 10).
- Installation and configuration of all desktop and notebook computers.
- Part of a team that manages software updates, installations and configuration.
- Configure and manage all network printing.
- Day-to-day tier 1, 2 and 3 helpdesk for company nationwide, 1200 users.
- Direct executive support.
- Responsible for copy room operation and management, including office supply ordering.
- NEC phone system ads, moves Changes.

# 2009-11 - Systems Administrator 2011-06 Integrated Rehabilitation Co

Integrated Rehabilitation Group, Mill Creek, Washington

- · Sole person responsible for 22 locations, 200+ users, 10 servers, VoIP phone system and 185 workstations.
- · Microsoft software Subject Matter Expert for entire company.
- · Manage the day-to-day internal services provided to users, including e-mail, network drives and applications.
- · Manage the day to day network functions and server usage to ensure a stable infrastructure.
- · Perform appropriate network software/hardware maintenance procedures including virus updates, system patches and software service pack upgrades.
- · Installation, configuration, implementation of all company workstations. Initiated and implemented a complete upgrade of all workstations from XP/Vista to Windows 7.

- · Design, installation, configuration of the server infrastructure, migrating from a single Small Business Server to an Essential Business server multi-server environment.
- · Successful Migration of Window infrastructure from a single server to mixture of physical and virtual servers, using VMware, Dell NAS and HP Servers.
- · Oversaw and designed complete overhaul of company phone system, migrating away from copper lines to a VoIP/Sip solution, savings the company 20k annually.
- · Manage day-to-day MITEL VoIP phone system configuration and administration.



# **Education**

Strategy Computers, Bellevue Washington
 MCSE Certification Program

2001-01 - Information Technology

2003-01 Seattle Community Colleges - Seattle, Washington



# **Certifications**

Мср